<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>web development on Jesse Khala I Web Development I Marketing</title>
    <link>https://jessekhala.com/tags/web-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in web development on Jesse Khala I Web Development I Marketing</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://jessekhala.com/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://jessekhala.com/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 12:36:39 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jessekhala.com/tags/web-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>🧑🏾‍💼 React Job Simulator: My First Impressions</title>
      <link>https://jessekhala.com/posts/react-job-simulator-my-first-impressions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 12:36:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jessekhala.com/posts/react-job-simulator-my-first-impressions/</guid>
      <description>Note: AI assistance was employed in refining this article.
  This summer, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to go from treating coding as a hobby to turning it into a profession. Let me explain. Over the last 2 years, I&amp;rsquo;ve been learning to code for mainly two reasons.
 Personal Growth Save money on my entrepreneurial projects  I&amp;rsquo;ve done a lot of reflection on what I enjoy and in which direction I want to move towards both personally and professionally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎚️ From React to Next.js Why I Made the Switch What I Learned</title>
      <link>https://jessekhala.com/posts/from-react-to-nextjs-why-i-made-the-switch-what-i-learned/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 17:48:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jessekhala.com/posts/from-react-to-nextjs-why-i-made-the-switch-what-i-learned/</guid>
      <description>Note: AI assistance was employed in crafting and refining the article.
 Switching Lanes: From React to Next.js In the competitive landscape of web development and digital marketing, the frameworks you choose can be your secret weapon for success. Originally captivated by React&amp;rsquo;s flexibility and robust community, I&amp;rsquo;ve recently transitioned to Next.js.
In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll unpack the strategic and technical reasons behind the move, look at some advantages of Next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🆙 I&#39;m React State, Lift Me Up, Asshole</title>
      <link>https://jessekhala.com/posts/im-react-state-lift-me-up-asshole/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 13:47:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jessekhala.com/posts/im-react-state-lift-me-up-asshole/</guid>
      <description>Note: AI assistance was employed in crafting the code snippets and refining this article. The inspiration came from the article: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m Comic Sans, Asshole&amp;rdquo;.
  Stop it. I said: &amp;ldquo;STOP. IT!&amp;rdquo;. Stupid. You have been re-rendering your TindasanaAI React component for the gazillionth time and the items you are selecting are always lost along the way. Well, it&amp;rsquo;s time to lift me up, asshole. You don&amp;rsquo;t understand why? Well, let me baby-feed this for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🛶 Navigating Web Development - Current Reflections</title>
      <link>https://jessekhala.com/posts/navigating-my-web-development-career-current-reflections/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:02:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jessekhala.com/posts/navigating-my-web-development-career-current-reflections/</guid>
      <description>I started getting back into Web Development at the end of 2021 after realizing that I enjoy understanding how modern web development works and noticing that no-code page builders overcharge for features that are sometimes just one little line of code. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, I like no-code website builders, they often save a lot of time, but they can get pricey if you just want a few extra features.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
